Hi Jerry, how are you fitting into your new role?
Hi Linda. The work has been very exciting.
Unfortunately, I'm having difficulty connecting
with my coworkers and new manager.
Oh no! What's the problem?
I don't know how I'm doing in my new position, and
I'm nervous about asking my manager for feedback.
I gotcha. You should really think of it as an
opportunity to hear about what you're doing well.
Ask for both positive and
constructive feedback from him.
Why are you having a difficult time
connecting with your coworkers?
I don't feel like I have much to connect on.
Everyone's a college grad and they've done
internships at all of these cool places.
I get how that can be uncomfortable,
but they'd be really interested to hear
a different kind of story to theirs.
Opening up will help you make stronger connections
here, and I'm sure your colleagues will surprise you too.
Is there anything else that is bothering you?
Yeah. I'm wondering why my manager
did not respond to one of my messages.
I was trying to be more open to him about some
of my ideas, but he didn't even respond.
Do you mind if I look over the message?
I can help and see what is going on.
Sure.
I can see what might have happened.
It's kind of hard to follow since it's so long.
Your manager probably needs some time to figure
out what the message and next steps are.
Well, I really wanted to talk about the information
I got from Materials & Company, our supplier.
They were telling me about all the benefits of stretch
aluminum, like the price, and that it's really thin.
That's the problem. I hear your excitement,
but not the actual message.
Here's how I'd restructure the message so that your manager
and I would be able to take action on this really great idea.
This is great feedback. I really appreciate it.
You have great ideas. Let's make sure
they're polished so that you shine here.